Sheldon, I've got to ask.
(Penny:)How did you figure out
that it was the geology lab?
(Sheldon:)Oh, simple.
The Arrah Arrah in the riddle
meant Jan Arrah,
(Sheldon:)a member of the Legion of
Superheroes known as Element Lad.
And then the word "He,"
it wasn't the masculine pronoun,
but rather, "H-E,"
the abbreviation for helium.
(Sheldon:)See where I'm going with this?
(Howard:)-Yes.
-Nice try.
(Sheldon:)Now, Element Lad's ability
(Sheldon:)is the power to transmute
chemical elements.
(Sheldon:)Helium has an atomic number of two.
(Sheldon:)If you multiply that by the
atomic number of "N," nitrogen,
(Sheldon:)you get 14, which is
the atomic number of...?
(Sheldon:)I'm just funnin' you, silicon.
And that is the most common element
(Sheldon:)in the Earth's surface.
So that narrowed it down
(Sheldon:)to the geology lab
or the chemistry lab.
(Howard:)Wow.
(Penny:)I can drink a beer underwater.
(Sheldon:)And I'm sure your parents are proud.
(Sheldon:)Now, finally, the line
"in this room the thing you'll see"